That in the vacation complex, all the prints are standing in such a way
submitting reports on the positive side.
These decisions are 3550, Quite,
Agriculture, 3480, Nomura, 3300 to 3275, Morgan
Stanley, 3150, only from me, which kept
doing 16700, but all the other reports are
looking much better than the subscribe commentary box estimate, ghee and a
little department, but that subscribe can
definitely be seen in the coming time,
subscribe to the stock of the entry point of growth, subscribe to the business, then
from his hand, if you look at Asian Paints, then it is
around 3334 in the range of ₹100,
but it is on this side and is
seen coming around 350-500 rupees, that
like every time, it is on the
side of forming around 750 rupees,
for four-five minutes at the second number from the serial - 07 has committed
suicide, it will submit so that like every time,
Goldman Sachs again goes negative
Neutral MP with stars, target is ₹500,
however, it is clear in the Parliament itself
that the numbers are
looking good and subscribe
should not subscribe that here in the next two
years, we are seeing a return of 28 per cent bullishness,
subscribe to the channel quickly, the
target on this topic is 7766 and it is visible,
I am late today, stick buy rating is 3315 rupees
from the formation, Morgan Stanley has
kept an overweight rating, target is 3236 rupees
and since this morning, the A* is coming out
from the negative report on the saver side, so first
Bajaj Finance Minister report, after that
now on the front which is celebrating 1293
for the target, so another reporter from their side from Andheri East,
but still I
need to maintain support, their rating is yes,
why not caring and all that
seems to be coming much better than expected,
amendments, a lot of twists have been made
regarding the near term outlook, different types of
their pack are also very positive,
those company's numbers, subscribe to the channel
And the subscribers are
seen laughing, there is only one sell
side meeting which is at 1293 strength, there is
no downgrade from the hospital soon, but they have kept either neutral stars
printing or pet site rating,
so it has been given buy equal I and
they have free target of Rs. 6250,
Morgan Stanley has kept overweight rating
at 6850, target is
5700 from agricultural experts, one Goldman Sachs has a rating of 5700 from this, in
this way they celebrated these
three cars 44 and 45 and God attractive
camp numbers in job agri holiday, at that
time the accused has been talked about, profit
from this thing appointment,
definitely subscribe soon, but they talked about the
value and urine numbers operating,
but still half of them are seen sitting on honey numbers in the coming time, that is why
if you go from this side also, then a
clear trend of around 65-66 ₹100 can be seen here, it has
happened